ADAM KIM SEC+ | CYSA+ | CSAP

Tenacious cybersecurity professional with 1 year of experience with remodeling security policies from planning to publication, threat hunting, and evaluating security posture to assemble security tools in preparation to implement a SOC launch.

Ascertained expanded knowledge in cybersecurity, network/desktop, and programming to target and resolve complex security challenges. Seeking to leverage recent cyber certifications and training to become your next cybersecurity professional.

Contact

Akim456@gmail.com

AtomKim.com

4 347-554-3119

in AdamKim456

Resv

Certifications

Nov. 2021 Sec+ | Security+ CompTIA Certification

Oct. 2021

CySA+ | Cyber Security
Analyst

CompTIA Certification

Nov. 2021

CSAP | Cyber Security Analytics Professional

CompTIA Certification

Aug. 2021 Cyber Security Essentials

Cisco Certification

Aug. 2021
Networking Essentials
Cisco Certification

Cisco Certification

Aug. 2021 Linux Essentials Cisco/NDG Certificate

Education

2021

Per Scholas, Bronx NY Cyber Security Analyst

2018

Per Scholas, Bronx NY Java Developer

2015

Queens College, Queens NY

B.A. Media Studies

Employment

Cascade Bicycle Club | Cascade.org

Seattle, WA Oct. 2021 - Current

Volunteer Cybersecurity Consultant

Procurement to increase current security posture and meet security objectives. From preparation to SOC implementation, a collaborated effort to secure the mission to bring people together to experience the joy of bicycling through transportation, recreation, and friendship.

- Conducted risk & vulnerability assessments of the company security posture
- · Advised best practices to operate inline with the NIST framework
- · Conducted research & preparation of security tools to meet company security objectives
- Oversaw installation and testing of a Security Onion & service/plugin integration
- Monitored and fine tuned the SIEM to improve accuracy against false alerts

The Law Offices of Kim & Associates Cybersecurity GRC

Queens, NY Sept. 2020 - Oct. 2021

Development and maintenance of network infrastructure, prioritized network availability and security for all employees within the company. Reduced network and endpoint issues, increased productivity, strengthened company security posture. Assigned to threat hunt and investigate insider threats. Collaborated directly with the DFS to develop cyber security polices in accordance to 23 NYCRR Part 500(e). Orchestrated business continuity procedures for all technologies within the company during the frequent shifts of the pandemic.

- · Routine analysis of malicious files and rogue devices
- Conducted threat hunting on potential IOCs (Itarian & event logs)
- Centralized EPP & EDR to monitor malware, unauthorized apps, and system patches
- Strengthened WAPS securely for employees and limited access to visitors
- Performed audits, documented devices, SN/MAC addresses, and versions
- Imaged/clone hardened copies to reduce redeployment times of compromised machines
- · Instructed acceptable use policy and security training
- Authored the 23 CRR-NY-500(e) cyber security policy to completion for the business, approved by the Department of Financial Services

Network Engineer

Jan. 2019 - Oct. 2021

- Redesigned physical and logical design of network infrastructure
- · Segmented and maintenance private NAS's and external cloud
- · Administered user access, subnetting, and static IPs
- Streamlined configurations for 20+ VoIP/analog phones, 5 printers, CCTV, and peripherals
- Assembled 25+ desktop PCs, troubleshooting, and responsible for equipment budgeting
- \bullet Converted 50+ office & home PCs overnight for remote, day 1 of the pandemic shutdown
- Developed automated scripts for employees and increased productivity and office morale
- Deployed telepresence systems for 5 conference rooms for court proceedings due to the shift of the pandemic